[
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            2,
            3,
            4
        ],
        "answer": "4",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            4,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": "6",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            8,
            9,
            6
        ],
        "answer": "8",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            8,
            9,
            10
        ],
        "answer": "10",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            10,
            11,
            12
        ],
        "answer": "12",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            12,
            13,
            14
        ],
        "answer": "14",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            16,
            17,
            14
        ],
        "answer": "16",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "answer": "18",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            18,
            19,
            20
        ],
        "answer": "20",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            20,
            21,
            22
        ],
        "answer": "22",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "2 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            24,
            25,
            22
        ],
        "answer": "24",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            4,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": "6",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            8,
            9,
            10
        ],
        "answer": "9",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            10,
            11,
            12
        ],
        "answer": "12",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            16,
            13,
            14,
            15
        ],
        "answer": "15",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "answer": "18",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "answer": "21",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            24,
            25,
            22
        ],
        "answer": "24",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            25,
            26,
            27
        ],
        "answer": "27",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            28,
            29,
            30
        ],
        "answer": "30",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            32,
            33,
            34
        ],
        "answer": "33",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "3 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            34,
            35,
            36
        ],
        "answer": "36",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            8,
            9,
            6
        ],
        "answer": "8",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            10,
            11,
            12
        ],
        "answer": "12",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            16,
            17,
            14
        ],
        "answer": "16",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            18,
            19,
            20
        ],
        "answer": "20",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            24,
            25,
            22
        ],
        "answer": "24",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            26,
            27,
            28
        ],
        "answer": "28",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            32,
            33,
            30
        ],
        "answer": "32",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            34,
            35,
            36
        ],
        "answer": "36",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            40,
            41,
            38
        ],
        "answer": "40",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            42,
            43,
            44
        ],
        "answer": "44",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "4 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            48,
            49,
            46
        ],
        "answer": "48",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            8,
            9,
            10
        ],
        "answer": "10",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            16,
            13,
            14,
            15
        ],
        "answer": "15",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            18,
            19,
            20
        ],
        "answer": "20",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            24,
            25,
            26
        ],
        "answer": "25",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            28,
            29,
            30
        ],
        "answer": "30",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            33,
            34,
            35
        ],
        "answer": "35",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            40,
            41,
            38
        ],
        "answer": "40",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            43,
            44,
            45
        ],
        "answer": "45",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            48,
            49,
            50
        ],
        "answer": "50",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            56,
            53,
            54,
            55
        ],
        "answer": "55",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "5 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            58,
            59,
            60
        ],
        "answer": "60",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            10,
            11,
            12
        ],
        "answer": "12",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "answer": "18",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            24,
            25,
            22
        ],
        "answer": "24",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            28,
            29,
            30
        ],
        "answer": "30",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            34,
            35,
            36
        ],
        "answer": "36",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            40,
            41,
            42
        ],
        "answer": "42",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            48,
            49,
            46
        ],
        "answer": "48",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            52,
            53,
            54
        ],
        "answer": "54",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            58,
            59,
            60
        ],
        "answer": "60",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            64,
            65,
            66
        ],
        "answer": "66",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "6 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            72,
            73,
            70
        ],
        "answer": "72",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            12,
            13,
            14
        ],
        "answer": "14",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "answer": "21",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            26,
            27,
            28
        ],
        "answer": "28",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            33,
            34,
            35
        ],
        "answer": "35",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            40,
            41,
            42
        ],
        "answer": "42",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            48,
            49,
            50
        ],
        "answer": "49",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            56,
            57,
            54
        ],
        "answer": "56",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            64,
            61,
            62,
            63
        ],
        "answer": "63",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            68,
            69,
            70
        ],
        "answer": "70",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            75,
            76,
            77
        ],
        "answer": "77",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "7 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            82,
            83,
            84
        ],
        "answer": "84",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            16,
            17,
            14
        ],
        "answer": "16",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            24,
            25,
            22
        ],
        "answer": "24",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            32,
            33,
            30
        ],
        "answer": "32",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            40,
            41,
            38
        ],
        "answer": "40",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            48,
            49,
            46
        ],
        "answer": "48",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            56,
            57,
            54
        ],
        "answer": "56",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            64,
            65,
            62
        ],
        "answer": "64",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            72,
            73,
            70
        ],
        "answer": "72",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            80,
            81,
            78
        ],
        "answer": "80",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            88,
            89,
            86
        ],
        "answer": "88",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "8 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            96,
            97,
            94
        ],
        "answer": "96",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "answer": "18",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            25,
            26,
            27
        ],
        "answer": "27",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            34,
            35,
            36
        ],
        "answer": "36",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            43,
            44,
            45
        ],
        "answer": "45",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            52,
            53,
            54
        ],
        "answer": "54",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            64,
            61,
            62,
            63
        ],
        "answer": "63",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            72,
            73,
            70
        ],
        "answer": "72",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            80,
            81,
            82
        ],
        "answer": "81",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            88,
            89,
            90
        ],
        "answer": "90",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            97,
            98,
            99
        ],
        "answer": "99",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "9 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            106,
            107,
            108
        ],
        "answer": "108",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            18,
            19,
            20
        ],
        "answer": "20",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            28,
            29,
            30
        ],
        "answer": "30",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            40,
            41,
            38
        ],
        "answer": "40",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            48,
            49,
            50
        ],
        "answer": "50",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            58,
            59,
            60
        ],
        "answer": "60",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            68,
            69,
            70
        ],
        "answer": "70",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            80,
            81,
            78
        ],
        "answer": "80",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            88,
            89,
            90
        ],
        "answer": "90",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            98,
            99,
            100
        ],
        "answer": "100",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            108,
            109,
            110
        ],
        "answer": "110",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "10 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            120,
            121,
            118
        ],
        "answer": "120",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            20,
            21,
            22
        ],
        "answer": "22",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            32,
            33,
            34
        ],
        "answer": "33",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            42,
            43,
            44
        ],
        "answer": "44",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            56,
            53,
            54,
            55
        ],
        "answer": "55",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            64,
            65,
            66
        ],
        "answer": "66",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            75,
            76,
            77
        ],
        "answer": "77",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            88,
            89,
            86
        ],
        "answer": "88",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            97,
            98,
            99
        ],
        "answer": "99",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            108,
            109,
            110
        ],
        "answer": "110",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            120,
            121,
            122
        ],
        "answer": "121",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "11 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            130,
            131,
            132
        ],
        "answer": "132",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 2 = ?",
        "choices": [
            24,
            25,
            22
        ],
        "answer": "24",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 3 = ?",
        "choices": [
            34,
            35,
            36
        ],
        "answer": "36",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 4 = ?",
        "choices": [
            48,
            49,
            46
        ],
        "answer": "48",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 5 = ?",
        "choices": [
            58,
            59,
            60
        ],
        "answer": "60",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 6 = ?",
        "choices": [
            72,
            73,
            70
        ],
        "answer": "72",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 7 = ?",
        "choices": [
            82,
            83,
            84
        ],
        "answer": "84",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 8 = ?",
        "choices": [
            96,
            97,
            94
        ],
        "answer": "96",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 9 = ?",
        "choices": [
            106,
            107,
            108
        ],
        "answer": "108",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 10 = ?",
        "choices": [
            120,
            121,
            118
        ],
        "answer": "120",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 11 = ?",
        "choices": [
            130,
            131,
            132
        ],
        "answer": "132",
        "time": 5
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "12 \u00d7 12 = ?",
        "choices": [
            144,
            145,
            142
        ],
        "answer": "144",
        "time": 5
    }
]